welcome ladies and gentlemen to our 16th
annual Halloween corn maze
as many of you are already aware we
eClinical are rated as the number one
corn maze in the entire [ __ ] country
it's because of this that every
Halloween we put everything we've got
into making the most spectacular corn
maze every year I see we've got quite
the turnout today
so before I explain the rules let me
show you all the prize that goes to the
first lucky man to make it out of the
corn maze
the first-place winner will get a use
worth of pumpkin pie made by my dear ol
grandma as well as a big ol spanking
from one of my beautiful pumpkin girls
how is it going [ __ ] does anybody
need a spanking from Marnie I heard
somebody's been a bad boy or if you
don't need a spankin I could always let
your big-ass bows Elaine every minute
without wind is my wish a little Drive
become a real kick so it can grab me
rolling sois Charles calm the [ __ ] down
whoa like sixty years old oh man I had
no idea that the number one prize would
be a year's worth of pumpkin pie I I
think I need to sit down for a second
I'm gonna [ __ ] my pants ha ha keep it in
your pants bro you didn't even win yet
hey announcer guy you better be careful
about bringing up food around my bro
he's so fat that he wouldn't even think
twice about writing your smelly ass for
a cheeseburger [ __ ] why are you getting
so excited over pumpkin pie I'm [ __ ]
rich if you want pumpkin pie just ask me
for it and I'll buy you a hundred years
worth of that [ __ ] that's not the point
Bart levy I'm tired of people like
Manic ‘ns Sonya calling me fat I want
to win this all by myself and prove to
them that I can work to get my own food
no you dumb [ __ ] just last week I
bought you McDonald's and it wasn't a
happy meal with an entire [ __ ]
restaurant and had it built right next
to your house then you complained and
cried like a [ __ ] because you were too
lazy to walk 10 feet to the
drive-through window pull down your
[ __ ] pants peach look at that ass
does that look like it belongs to
somebody who works for his food
nope that's the ass of somebody who sits
on the couch all day and waits for food
to be brought to him
of course who says that's a bad thing
we'll all participants please gather
round
one of my beautiful pumpkin girls is
going to start explaining the rules so
you don't want to miss this [ __ ] get to
work [ __ ] and don't forget to shake
your milk jugs while you're at it I'm
not paying you to just stand around and
act all sexy but but daddy not paying me
at all and how long are we going to be
doing this also I'm only 12 years old
and I need to get to school
will everybody please look at the paper
that you were given when you first
arrived here to win the years worth of
delicious pumpkin pie you will need to
get for pumpkins stamps and also be the
first one out of the maze to win now
some of you may be wondering how to get
those stamps I'll take it from here
[ __ ]
I know eating off all those rules is
hard for you since women are not good at
reading you go back over there with the
other pumpkin girls and show off your
sexy butt crack or some [ __ ]
hidden inside the maze are four
checkpoints at each of these checkpoints
is one of my pumpkin boys to get a
pumpkin stamp you need to find the for
pumpkin boys that are hidden throughout
the maze all you have to do is ask them
for a pumpkin stamp and they will give
you one once you get all four pumpkin
stamps all you have to do is race to the
end and you win oh I've got a question
what do the pumpkin boys look like how
do we know when we find one are the
pumpkin boys wearing just their
underwear too
they better be or else I'll feel like
I'm being ripped off this corn maze is
costing me $800 for a single [ __ ]
ticket the last thing I need to tell you
is be careful of evil pumpkin man
they're in pumpkin man what the [ __ ] is
that the pumpkin man is an individual
separate from the pumpkin boys if he
finds you he will beat me up and drag
you all the way back to the beginning of
the maze oh my God
the evil pumpkin man sounds so scary
what if he jumps out to try and scare us
I'm afraid I will piss myself all up in
my brand-new bikini don't worry about it
sugar tits daddy Manic is here to
protect you and your big-ass boobies the
moment I pull this trigger the race will
officially begin on your mark get set
wait you guys look over there do you
think that's one of the pumpkin boys it
has to be
look at that dude pumpkin costume
excuse me are you one of the pumpkin
boys can we please have a stamp what do
you think [ __ ] well hurry it up pull
out your stamp sheet so I can get this
job over with so I can go home and beat
my wife for not making me my macaroni
and cheese for dinner last night like
she promised she would
oh my God holy [ __ ] [ __ ]
I don't think I have ever seen such big
boobies in my whole life
ah ha ha do you like what you see
pumpkin boy they are quite big and juicy
aren't they yes
they um I'm not really allowed to do
this but if you do something for me
[ __ ]
I might just consider giving you another
stamp free of charge
I'll have to share what it is first
although haha I'm one bad girl who's up
for anything well it's it's a bit of a
fetish of mine I suppose good the
crazier the better are you going to poop
all over me now hold the [ __ ] up if you
are going to give that [ __ ] an extra
stamp we all want in on this that's fine
this is something you can all
participate in well go on pumpkinboy
what is it that we need to do
well it's kinda embarrassing just a
silly little wish I've always had I
guess you could say it's it's my most
biggest dream in the whole wide world
I've always wanted a girl with big
boobies to dress up as Yuki moto from
ukyo and spank my ass while I'm dressed
up as Seto Kaiba
okay are you kids ready to do this cause
it's going down whether you like it or
not
okay but you still never told us why we
have to wear these costumes haha are you
[ __ ] or some [ __ ] you're Yuki's duel
monsters your job is to cheer Yuki on as
he's raping me what the [ __ ] are you
just standing there for do you want your
damn stamps or not
[Music]
Mindi when they come back oh my God
hayden go check it out Sleet must be
really far behind us what do you say we
hide in the corn and scare him when he
walks by I bet he'll [ __ ] his pants why
would we want to do that Robotnik
shouldn't we focus on winning the years
worth of pumpkin pie [ __ ] a corn mazes
into real corn maze unless if somebody
gets so scared that they should their
pants everybody knows that now are you
going to help me scare him or would you
rather lick Taco Bell hot sauce off my
cheeks when we get back home
well Taco Bell hot sauce is pretty spicy
[ __ ] here he comes quick Dingo into the
bushes
but dr. Robotnik why are you taking off
your clothes didn't you say we're just
going to scare him I don't pay you to us
questions [ __ ] I pay you to follow
orders
dr. Robotnik link Oh
come on bro do you see her yet not yet
bro I need you to lift me just a little
bit higher I can't go any higher oh my
God
what the hell do you kids think you are
doing over there do you want to get us
thrown out we are just trying to look
for Mindy mom this corn maze isn't fun
anymore how long do we have to be here I
want to go home
so Leah how many times do I have to tell
you not to eat the corn off the ground
what it what the [ __ ] is wrong with you
y'all stupid here
don't your weapon it lets them know your
[ __ ] mother eat
Charles quit yelling at my kids just go
home yeah drunk as [ __ ]
I ain't drunk woman and Riario defendant
Axl Elena
oh [ __ ] he's got a gun
you
what the hell did you do Charles you
killed one of the pumpkin boys it's not
my fault
you was aiming for Sonya what are we
gonna do mama are we gonna get in
trouble not if you don't say [ __ ] Sonic
Manic get a shovel we're burying this
[ __ ]
you
sorry [ __ ] but if you want to win a
game like this you can't always play
fair
so long suckers
[Laughter]
why are you crying
[ __ ] why do you think I'm trying a
pumpkin boy just farted in my face hey
[ __ ] have you seen any pumpkin boys
around here
oh hey Knuckles it's you I see you're
alone did your friends they cheer to
Knuckles the cool kid that doesn't have
friends
he only has [ __ ] haha yeah me too
I was just kidding my friends wouldn't
ditch me stop crying
[ __ ] so are you like a [ __ ] why are
you so short what the [ __ ] did you just
call me you're so lucky with your height
you're always staring straight at Bart
Levy's butt cheeks not words come for
here I found another one of those sexy
pumpkin boys
oh man you are so hot easily the hottest
pumpkin boy I am at today is that so I
guess I must be hot as [ __ ] then hey
daddy
I know it's against the rules but what
do you say you give me an extra stamp
sorry that rule especially applies to
huge [ __ ]
you
my pipe and who might you be sorry
I couldn't help but notice that you were
staring at my ass I was only staring at
your ass the cause you've got a sick
pumpkin tattoo
haha sure that was the only reason let's
go with that do silly boy what's your
name [ __ ]
I'm Sleet but my friends call me wolf
storm blade because that's my wizard
name and wizard101 that's a nice name
[ __ ] I like that name
do you do anything for fun I don't know
I mean I'm a bounty hunter so I kill
people I guess well what a coincidence I
once killed a man too in fact I just got
out of jail after spending 20 years
listen are you going to give us a
pumpkin stamp or are we going to have a
[ __ ] problem I ain't giving you [ __ ]
until you bend over and let me shove it
in your ass oh yeah I'm gonna enjoy this
do you know why I applied for this job
why I became a pumpkin bought because in
the middle of a cornfield no one can
hear you scream come here [ __ ]
[Music]
with the [ __ ] you around missus not you
dr. Robotnik what happened to you
where's Dingo it was the pumpkin man he
just showed up out of nowhere and
started beating me up he dragged him go
all the way back to the beginning of the
maze he tried to drag me back to but I
was so fat so he just gave up after 15
minutes
poor guy it's unfortunate that he died
so young is what this our own even they
would lots of bitches o Danube guys I
think I got some blood on my shirt
that's not good
if the police find evidence or DNA from
the victim honest irises are going
straight to the jail as we better remove
our clothes so the police cannot pin
anything on us
everybody remove your clothes and place
them into a pile we're burying that [ __ ]
with the body while you kids focus on
doing that I'll go get you a change of
clothes from the car if they see that
your clothes are gone they could suspect
something let's pick up the pace [ __ ]
we can't afford for anyone to find out
what we are doing you'd better shut that
hole under your nose [ __ ] this is our
lives on the line here so grab the
shovel and do your job that's our says
for you bro a weak-ass [ __ ] she'll
probably tell the police to kill her my
fat bro the Hedgehog family has no use
for poopy babies like her I can't bro
mom would ground us for like two weeks
it looks like you ain't got a choice get
to work [ __ ]
wherever a problem kids so my owners
coming down T but but we didn't finish
burying the body
what the hell should we make a dash for
it no egos tell him
yo Trey finish up early what we as this
Kornberg knock it down and worrier a tip
that stanky is where tourtière sue
Moroney whoa was today yo better
communal he know so nobody is watching
me what your [ __ ] badge or Semitic Oh
No it was a gang war in TFA osika
okay what intervals oh it's a boy sonar
on leave a boot from oh it has a message
on back
it can only rain this most many antes
del mediodía know is current target a
Muslim he can't achieve a couch attaboy
so my vision is ours
but first burglary play us a survey me
Hey look over there
I think we got to the end of the corn
maze and I think we are the first ones
to so how many pumpkin stamps did you
guys get remember you need four of them
to win the prize I only got one but I
don't care because I got to hang out
with all of you today I only got two I
got well for them because I would for to
have sex with the pumpkin boys for extra
ones but I lost my stamp sheet a few
minutes ago maybe one of the pumpkin
boys shut it up in my butt crack I wish
I could say that I'm surprised but I'm
not I have three what about you Sonic
you're oddly quiet Hey how many stamps
you got man hee hee well I don't have
enough to win I only have two I'll just
go one out through the exit and get a
third stamp see you guys on the outside
good job Knuckles you are going to share
the pies with me your best bud aren't
you
that fat-ass has three stamps he's going
to take the win you slippery little
[ __ ] hey you better get back here hurry
bro free you ain't going anywhere [ __ ]
boy you thought you could trick me dumb
[ __ ] well think again now let's start
over
how many pumpkin stands do you really
have one two three oh dear you were
lying to me you know Sonic
my great-grandfather Athair the great
sage Althea kidness always taught me
that lying boys need to be punished what
the hell is going on out here
is he slapping that blue man's ass I
know right it's so [ __ ] sexy
yes beat his ass stop it Knuckles stop
it what did that blue man do tell you I
hope today you learned that while I
can't be the nicest person you'll ever
meet
I can also be your worst nightmare don't
you double-cross me Knuckles the cool
Echidna
after a long day we finally have our
champion once you must eat this 4th
and final stamp the pumpkin pies and
pumpkin ladies will all yours
hold that thought
unfortunately for you I have to announce
but I just bought this corn maze for 800
trillion dollar
now the tire I'm the new owner I believe
a change of rules is in order the number
of stamps no longer determines the
winner the winner and the one that get
all the pies is the one with the biggest
ass
[Applause]
you're not that blue ever you eat
they'll caches minifee okay
and that was the story of how I Sonic
the Hedgehog and lover of Bart levy
Montclair up president won the great
corn maze competition and won all of
those juicy pumpkin pies
[Music]
and even though it was a long time ago I
still treasure this wonderful memory
[Music]
you